http://www.mmv.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Research & DevelopmentMMV-supported projectsR&D areas of workNext-generation medicinesProducts for key populationsWorking with regulatorsInformation for scientistsCall for proposalsTPPs & TCPsLearning resources for discovery scientistsProject of the year awardComputational chemistryGlobal health compound design webinarsR&D challengesAccessProducts & projectsAreas of workSupporting introductionEnhancing reachInforming R&DGathering market intelligenceProduct mapsTool KitsInjectable Artesunate tool kitArtesunate rectal capsules tool kitSeasonal Malaria Chemoprevention tool kitThe road to health impactAccess challengesPartneringOur partner networkThe PDP modelSocially responsible agreementsOur clinical centre partnersOur donorsCurrent donorsPast donorsDonate to MMVOur impactAchievementsReal life storiesAbout usWhat we doAn overview of our workOur strategic focusOur historyPeople & governanceStaff biosStaff mapStaff interviewsBoard of DirectorsMMV North America BoardExpert Scientific Advisory CommitteeAccess & Product Management Advisory CommitteeGlobal Safety BoardWork with usJobsRFPs/RFIsMMV's internship programmePoliciesDiversity at MMVFunding and expenditureFAQsContact usMalaria & medicinesDefinitions and symptomsFive speciesParasite lifecycleMalaria facts & figuresMalaria treatmentHistory of antimalarialsOptimizing artemisinin productionMalaria online courseNewsroomNews & Press ReleasesFilmsInfographicsInterviewsImage slideshowsPublicationsAudioEventsMMV OpenMalaria LibreAbout Malaria LibreParticipate in Malaria LibreMalaria Libre data repositoryCOVID BoxAbout the COVID BoxRequest the COVID boxSupporting informationCOVID Box terms and conditionsPandemic Response BoxAbout the Pandemic Response BoxRequest the Pandemic Response BoxSupporting informationTerms & conditionsPathogen BoxAbout the Pathogen BoxExploiting the Pathogen BoxPathogen Box researchSupporting informationTerms & conditionsMalaria BoxAbout the Malaria BoxMalaria Box ResearchSupporting informationTerms & conditionsMap of box ordersFollow-up guidelinesOpen Source Drug DiscoveryMMV Open TeamContact us
HomePrivacy policy
Privacy policy
MMV is committed to protect your privacy by collecting the minimum amount of information about you. This Privacy Policy sets out how we use and protect any personal information that you give us when using our website.
What personal data do we collect?
We may collect personal information about you such as your name, email address, CV or any information you send via this website.
We may also collect personal information from our website visitors by using cookies and Google Analytics to help us improve the content of our website. You have the ability to disable cookies in your browser, but if you do, certain functionalities may be impaired. For more information on how to disable cookies, please refer to your browser’s cookie section and to Google Analytics’ Terms.
What do we do with the information you provided?
We use your personal information:
to properly respond to your enquiries
to properly respond to your job application
for administrative purposes
How do we protect your personal data?
All reasonable precautions have been taken to prevent unauthorized access to, loss or misuse of your personal information. Your data will be securely stored. MMV has put in place procedures to safeguard and secure your personal information; this safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details.
Who has access to your personal data?
We do not sell, nor disclose, any personal information obtained from this website to third parties for commercial purposes. However, we may use this information to keep in contact with you and inform you of developments associated with our activities. You will be given the opportunity to remove yourself from any mailing list. If at any time in the future we wish to disclose information collected on this website to any third party, it will only be with your knowledge and consent.
What are your privacy rights?
You have the right to:
access your personal data
correct your personal data
have your personal data erased
object to the use of your personal data
restrict the use of your personal data
request the transfer of your personal data to you or a third party
withdraw your consent to the use of your personal data at any time where we are relying on consent to process your personal data.
If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at privacy [at] mmv.org.
How long do we keep your personal data?
We will keep your personal information for as long as is necessary to meet the purposes for which it was collected, after which time it will be deleted from our systems, unless we are legally required to hold some information to fulfil our legal obligations.
Links to other websites
This website may contain links to other websites of interest. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites may have their own privacy policies and that we cannot be responsible for the privacy and protection of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites. Please read carefully these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please email us at privacy [at] mmv.org.
It is important that personal data we hold about you is accurate and up-to-date. Please keep us informed if your personal data changes or if you wish your personal data be removed from any list under our control.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
MMV may revise this Policy from time to time without advance notice. Any changes to our Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We invite you to carefully read this Policy each time you use the website to ensure that it still meets with your approval.
This Privacy Policy was last updated on 26 June 2018.
RSS subscribe
Printer friendly
